Guide to the Howard Zinn Papers TAM.542
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series IV: Appearances / Speaking Engagements, 1964-2008
  - Appearances / Speaking Engagements, 2001; cuid15800 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Appearances / Speaking Engagements, 2002; cuid15801 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Appearances / Speaking Engagements, 2003; cuid15802 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Appearances / Speaking Engagements, 2004; cuid15803 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Appearances / Speaking Engagements, 2005; cuid15804 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Appearances / Speaking Engagements, 2006-2008; cuid15805 (Box 18, Folder 16)
- Series V: Boston University, 1960-2003
  The first Boston University (BU) subseries focuses on Howard Zinn's teaching career including course syllabi, a few lecture transcripts, a number of his annual appointment forms and student evaluations of his teaching for the years 1969 through 1983. There are many examples of student work – papers, projects, journals and independent study – and a good deal of associated materials. The student journals not only provide a glimpse into the conduct of Zinn's classes and the materials he used, but also reveal reactions of the individual students.
  The second, and much larger subseries, documents many crises and controversies that occurred during Zinn's time at BU including suppression of academic freedom and civil liberties, censorship of campus press, attempts to build and strengthen the AAUP and other unions on campus, tenure and salary grievances, strikes and demonstrations, issues surrounding various University trustees and many examples of the rancor between Zinn and John Silber, former BU president. Some of the conflicts continue even after Zinn's retirement, including his active opposition to Silber's gubernatorial candidacy in 1990. It should be noted that material concerning specific controversies may be found in multiple folders. An event might, for example, appear in a general controversies folder, in a folder focused on the Committee to Save Boston University, in a folder addressing AAUP activities and in a folder titled with the name of the particular issue.
  - Subseries V:A: Teaching and Student Material, 1964-2003
    - Boston University Faculty Committee on Social Issues: Areas of Interest, 1966-1967; cuid15806 (Box 18, Folder 17)
    - Course Syllabi: "Introduction to Political Theory", 1968-1987; cuid15807 (Box 18, Folder 18)
    - Course Syllabi: "Law and Justice in America", 1970-1987; cuid15808 (Box 18, Folder 19)
    - Course Syllabi: Marxism Seminar, "Marxism and Anarchism", 1968-1984; cuid15809 (Box 18, Folder 20)
    - Course Syllabi: "Politics and History", 1969, 1979-1988; cuid15810 (Box 18, Folder 21)
    - Course Syllabi: Various, 1969, 1974-1988, 2003, undated; cuid15811 (Box 18, Folder 22)
    - Letters of Appreciation, 1977-1987; cuid15812 (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Office Memoranda, 1978, 1986, undated; cuid15813 (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - The Point, A Guide for Students and Faculty in College Two, 1973; cuid15814 (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Student Evaluations of Zinn, 1969-1977; cuid15815 (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Student Evaluations of Zinn, 1979; cuid15816 (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - Student Evaluations of Zinn, 1980; cuid15817 (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - Student Evaluations of Zinn, 1981; cuid15818 (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - Student Evaluations of Zinn, 1985-1987; cuid15819 (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - Student Evaluations of Zinn, undated; cuid15820 (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - Student Evaluations of Zinn - Metropolitan College, 1980; cuid15821 (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - Student Evaluations of Zinn - Metropolitan College (Spring), 1981; cuid15822 (Box 19, Folder 11)
    - Student Evaluations of Zinn - Metropolitan College (Fall), 1981; cuid15823 (Box 19, Folder 12)
    - Student Evaluations of Zinn - Metropolitan College (Spring), 1982; cuid15824 (Box 19, Folder 13)
    - Student Evaluations of Zinn - Metropolitan College (Fall), 1982; cuid15825 (Box 19, Folder 14)
    - Student Evaluations of Zinn - Metropolitan College (Spring), 1983; cuid15826 (Box 19, Folder 15)
    - Student Evaluations of Zinn - Metropolitan College (Fall), 1983; cuid15827 (Box 19, Folder 16)
    - Zinn Annual Appointment Forms, 1976-1981; cuid15828 (Box 19, Folder 17)
    - Zinn Lecture Transcripts: "Wealth and Law" Lecture One and Two, undated; cuid15829 (Box 19, Folder 18)
    - Zinn Sabbatical, 1977-1978; cuid15830 (Box 19, Folder 19)
    - Zinn Student Letters, 1974-1982, undated; cuid15831 (Box 19, Folder 20)
    - Zinn Student Work: Correspondence (alienated), 1964, 1975, undated; cuid15832 (Box 19, Folder 21)
    - Zinn Student Work: Independent Study, 1981; cuid15833 (Box 19, Folder 22)
    - Zinn Student Work: Independent Study, 1982; cuid15834 (Box 19, Folder 23)
    - Zinn Student Work: Independent Study, [1982], undated; cuid15835 (Box 19, Folder 24)
    - Zinn Student Work: Journals, 1982; cuid15836 (Box 19, Folder 25)
    - Zinn Student Work: Journals, 1983; cuid15837 (Box 19, Folder 26)
    - Zinn Student Work: Journals, 1985-1986; cuid15838 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Zinn Student Work: Journals, 1987; cuid15839 (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Zinn Student Work: Journals, 1988; cuid15840 (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Zinn Student Work: Journals, undated; cuid15841 (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - Zinn Student Work: Papers, 1968-1975; cuid15842 (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - Zinn Student Work: Papers, 1976; cuid15843 (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - Zinn Student Work: Papers, 1979-1980; cuid15844 (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Zinn Student Work: Papers, 1981; cuid15845 (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - Zinn Student Work: Papers, 1982, 1984; cuid15846 (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - Zinn Student Work: Papers, undated; cuid15847 (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - Zinn Student Work: Projects (includes letter from Senator Harry F. Byrd), 1972-1978; cuid15848 (Box 20, Folder 11)
    - Zinn Student Work: Projects, 1981-1985, undated; cuid15849 (Box 20, Folder 12)
    - Zinn Student Work: Projects - Associated Material, 1969; cuid15850 (Box 20, Folder 13)
    - Zinn Student Work: Projects - Associated Material, 1972-1973; cuid15851 (Box 20, Folder 14)
    - Zinn Student Work: Projects - Associated Material (I), 1974; cuid15852 (Box 20, Folder 15)
    - Zinn Student Work: Projects - Associated Material (II), 1974; cuid15853 (Box 20, Folder 16)
    - Zinn Student Work: Projects - Associated Material (includes print/artist's proof "Squeaky Fromme..."), 1975-1977; cuid15854 (Box 20, Folder 17)
    - Zinn Student Work: Projects - Associated Material, 1978; cuid15855 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - Zinn Student Work: Projects - Associated Material, 1979; cuid15856 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - Zinn Student Work: Projects - Associated Material, 1980; cuid15857 (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Zinn Student Work: Projects - Associated Material, 1981; cuid15858 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Zinn Student Work: Projects - Associated Material, 1982; cuid15859 (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Zinn Student Work: Projects - Associated Material, 1983, 1984; cuid15860 (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - Zinn Student Work: Projects - Associated Material, 1985; cuid15861 (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - Zinn Student Work: Projects - Associated Material (I), 1986; cuid15862 (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - Zinn Student Work: Projects - Associated Material (II), 1986; cuid15863 (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - Zinn Student Work: Projects - Associated Material, 1987; cuid15864 (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - Zinn Student Work: Projects - Associated Material, undated; cuid15865 (Box 21, Folder 11)
    - Zinn Student Work: Projects/Papers (Housing and Tenant Issues), 1968-1972; cuid15866 (Box 21, Folder 12)
    - Zinn Student Work: Projects/Papers (Housing and Tenant Issues), 1982; cuid15867 (Box 21, Folder 13)
    - Zinn Student Work: Projects/Papers (Housing and Tenant Issues), undated; cuid15868 (Box 21, Folder 14)
    - Zinn Student Work: "Struggle to Survive: A History of the Exposure's Rebirth and the Graphics and Exploits of Jeff Smith", [1982]; cuid15869 (Box 21, Folder 15)
    - Zinn Student Work: Various Items, 1988, undated; cuid15870 (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Subseries V:B: Boston University Controversy, 1962-2002
    - Academic Freedom and the Boston University 5 (BU5), 1979-1980, undated; cuid15871 (Box 21, Folder 17)
    - Academic Freedom and the Boston University 5 (BU5): Legal Proceedings, 1979-1980, undated; cuid15872 (Box 21, Folder 18)
    - Academic Freedom and the Boston University 5 (BU5): "Materials"; "Documents and Clippings", 1976-1980, undated; cuid15873 (Box 21, Folder 19)
    - Academic Freedom and the Boston University 5 (BU5): Outdoor Class Attendees, 1979; cuid15874 (Box 21, Folder 20)
    - Academic Freedom and the Boston University 5 (BU5): Support (groups), 1979-1980; cuid15875 (Box 21, Folder 21)
    - Academic Freedom and the Boston University 5 (BU5): Support (individuals), 1979-1980; cuid15876 (Box 21, Folder 22)
    - Academic Freedom and the Boston University 5 (BU5): Support (Luria petitions), 1979; cuid15877 (Box 21, Folder 23)
    - Academic Freedom and the Boston University 5 (BU5): Support - Various Flyers, Lists, Notes and Other Related Material, 1979-1980, undated; cuid15878 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - American Association of University Professors (AAUP) Materials, 1974-1975; cuid15879 (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - American Association of University Professors (AAUP) Materials, 1976-1977; cuid15880 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - American Association of University Professors (AAUP) Materials (I), 1978-1979; cuid15881 (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - American Association of University Professors (AAUP) Materials (II), 1978-1979; cuid15882 (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - American Association of University Professors (AAUP) Materials (III), 1978-1979; cuid15883 (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - American Association of University Professors (AAUP) Materials, 1979-1980; cuid15884 (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - American Association of University Professors (AAUP) Materials, 1980; cuid15885 (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - American Association of University Professors (AAUP) Materials, 1980-1981, undated; cuid15886 (Box 22, Folder 9)
    - American Association of University Professors (AAUP) Materials (I), 1981; cuid15887 (Box 22, Folder 10)
    - American Association of University Professors (AAUP) Materials (II), 1981; cuid15888 (Box 22, Folder 11)
    - American Association of University Professors (AAUP) Materials, 1983-1985, undated; cuid15889 (Box 22, Folder 12)
    - Anti-War (Vietnam), 1968-1973; cuid15890 (Box 22, Folder 13)
    - Anti-War (Vietnam): Police Action March 27, 1972, cuid15891 (Box 22, Folder 14)
    - Banner Hanging Dispute: Abramowitz, Yosef I. et al. v. Trustees of Boston University, 1986; cuid15892 (Box 22, Folder 15)
    - Bias against Zinn, [1974]-1980, undated; cuid15893 (Box 22, Folder 16)
    - Boston University Controversy, 1965-1970; cuid15894 (Box 22, Folder 17)
    - Boston University Controversy, 1972-1979; cuid15895 (Box 22, Folder 18)
    - Boston University Controversy, 1980-1981; cuid15896 (Box 22, Folder 19)
    - Boston University Controversy, 1982; cuid15897 (Box 22, Folder 20)
    - Boston University Controversy, 1983; cuid15898 (Box 22, Folder 21)
    - Boston University Controversy, 1985; cuid15899 (Box 22, Folder 22)
    - Boston University Controversy, 1986-1989; cuid15900 (Box 22, Folder 23)
    - Boston University Controversy, 1990-1996; cuid15901 (Box 22, Folder 24)
    - Boston University Controversy, 1991-2002, undated; cuid15902 (Box 22, Folder 25)
    - Boston University Labor Council (BULC), 1979-1980, undated; cuid15903 (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - Budget / Financial Issues, 1976-1979, undated; cuid15904 (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - Budget / Financial Issues, 1976-1986, undated; cuid15905 (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - Building and Grounds Workers (SEIU, Local 254), 1977-1979; cuid15906 (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - Building and Grounds Workers (SEIU, Local 254): Strike, 1978; cuid15907 (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - Building and Grounds Workers (SEIU, Local 254): Strike - Press, 1978; cuid15908 (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - Campus Media: the bu exposure, 1977-1984, undated; cuid15909 (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - Campus Media: the bu exposure - Articles from the bu exposure and Daily Free Press, 1977-1983; cuid15910 (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - Campus Media: the bu exposure - the bu exposure Collective v. John Silber, et al., 1978-1983; cuid15911 (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - Campus Media: the bu exposure - the bu exposure Collective v. John Silber, et al. - Silber Deposition, 1982; cuid15912 (Box 23, Folder 10)
    - Campus Media: WBUR, 1977-1978, 1986; cuid15913 (Box 23, Folder 11)
    - Central Intelligence Agency, 1974-1987; cuid15914 (Box 23, Folder 12)
    - Chronology of Daily Free Press Items, [1985]; cuid15915 (Box 23, Folder 13)
    - Civil Liberties - Clippings, 1972-1986; cuid15916 (Box 23, Folder 14)
    - Civil Liberties Union of Massachusetts (CLUM) Inquiry and Report, 1979; cuid15917 (Box 23, Folder 15)
    - Civil Liberties Union of Massachusetts (CLUM) Inquiry and Report - Related Material, 1976-1980, undated; cuid15918 (Box 23, Folder 16)
    - Committee to Save Boston University, 1973-1980, undated; cuid15919 (Box 23, Folder 17)
    - Committee to Save Boston University, 1974-1980; cuid15920 (Box 23, Folder 18)
    - Committee to Save Boston University, 1979-1980; cuid15921 (Box 23, Folder 19)
    - Committee to Save Boston University, 1979-1980, undated; cuid15922 (Box 23, Folder 20)
    - Committee to Save Boston University, 1980, undated; cuid15923 (Box 23, Folder 21)
    - Committee to Save Boston University: Lists and Related Materials, 1979, undated; cuid15924 (Box 23, Folder 22)
    - Committee to Save Boston University: State Senator Gerard D'Amico, 1980; cuid15925 (Box 23, Folder 23)
    - Department of Political Science, 1974-1975; cuid15926 (Box 23, Folder 24)
    - Diamandopoulos, Peter, 1997-1999; cuid15927 (Box 23, Folder 25)
    - Draft Registration and Financial Aid, 1983; cuid15928 (Box 23, Folder 26)
    - Draft Registration and Financial Aid: Doe, John and Paul Poe v. Trustees of BU and Silber (I), 1983; cuid15929 (Box 23, Folder 27)
    - Draft Registration and Financial Aid: Doe, John and Paul Poe v. Trustees of BU and Silber (II), 1983; cuid15930 (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - Faculty Council Opposition to Duarte Honorary Degree (and Silber response), 1986; cuid15931 (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - Faculty Tenure, Appointments, 1969-1987, undated; cuid15932 (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - Faculty Tenure, Appointments: Bottome, Edgar, 1970, 1972; cuid15933 (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - Faculty Tenure, Appointments: Giroux, Henry, 1982-1983; cuid15934 (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - Lists, Various, 1980-1988, undated; cuid15935 (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - Marcuse, Herbert (substitute for Zinn), 1974; cuid15936 (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - "Mismanagement and Corruption", 1978-1990; cuid15937 (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - Newspapers: the bu exposure, 1977; cuid15938 (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - Newspapers: the bu exposure, 1978; cuid15939 (Box 24, Folder 10)
    - Newspapers: the bu exposure, 1979; cuid15940 (Box 24, Folder 11)
    - Newspapers: the bu exposure, 1980, 1983; cuid15941 (Box 24, Folder 12)
    - Newspapers: The Daily Free Press, 1972, 1977, 1978; cuid15942 (Box 24, Folder 13)
    - Newspapers: The Daily Free Press, Jan 1979-Feb 1979; cuid15943 (Box 24, Folder 14)
    - Newspapers: The Daily Free Press, Mar 1979-Apr 1979; cuid15944 (Box 24, Folder 15)
    - Newspapers: The Daily Free Press, Oct 1979-Apr 1981; cuid15945 (Box 24, Folder 16)
    - Nursing School Closure, 1987; cuid15946 (Box 24, Folder 17)
    - Photograph (Howard Zinn, Frances Fox Piven, Murray Levin), 1977; cuid15947 (Box 85, Folder 5)
    - "Pursuing Excellence at Boston University" by Frances Piven, Murray Levin and Howard Zinn, 1975; cuid15948 (Box 24, Folder 18)
    - Redmont, Bernard S., 1985-1986; cuid15949 (Box 24, Folder 19)
    - "Report of the Boston University Faculty Council on Academic Freedom", 1996; cuid15950 (Box 24, Folder 20)
    - Reserve Officer Training Corps (ROTC) and Military Recruitment, 1972; cuid15951 (Box 24, Folder 21)
    - Reserve Officer Training Corps (ROTC) and Military Recruitment, 1972-1974, undated; cuid15952 (Box 24, Folder 22)
    - Reserve Officer Training Corps (ROTC) and Military Recruitment, 1973; cuid15953 (Box 24, Folder 23)
    - Reserve Officer Training Corps (ROTC) and Military Recruitment, 1976, 1980, 1984; cuid15954 (Box 24, Folder 24)
    - Reserve Officer Training Corps (ROTC) and Military Recruitment, undated; cuid15955 (Box 24, Folder 25)
    - Silber, John: Arson Accusation against Howard Zinn, 1972, 1979-1980; cuid15956 (Box 24, Folder 26)
    - Silber, John: Articles, Various, 1972-1979; cuid15957 (Box 24, Folder 27)
    - Silber, John: Articles, Various, 1972-1990, undated; cuid15958 (Box 24, Folder 28)
    - Silber, John: Articles, Various, 1980-1987; cuid15959 (Box 24, Folder 29)
    - Silber, John: Articles, Various, 1993-1995, undated; cuid15960 (Box 24, Folder 30)
    - Silber, John: Faculty Call for Removal of Silber, 1979-1980; cuid15961 (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - Silber, John: Faculty Call for Removal of Silber - Outside Support (alumni), 1979-1980; cuid15962 (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - Silber, John: Faculty Call for Removal of Silber - Outside Support (includes letter from Henry Steele Commager), 1979; cuid15963 (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - Silber, John: Letters, Letters to Editor re: Silber, 1976-1979, 1989-1999, undated; cuid15964 (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - Silber, John: Massachusetts Gubernatorial Race, 1989-1990; cuid15965 (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - Silber, John: Massachusetts Gubernatorial Race - "Factbook on John Silber", 1990; cuid15966 (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - Silber, John: Massachusetts Gubernatorial Race - "Factbook on John Silber" - General, 1990; cuid15967 (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - Silber, John: Massachusetts Gubernatorial Race - "Factbook on John Silber" - Raw Materials (I), 1990; cuid15968 (Box 25, Folder 8)
    - Silber, John: Massachusetts Gubernatorial Race - "Factbook on John Silber" - Raw Materials (II), 1990; cuid15969 (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - Silber, John: Massachusetts Gubernatorial Race - "Factbook on John Silber" - Raw Materials (III), 1990; cuid15970 (Box 25, Folder 10)
    - Silber, John: Massachusetts Gubernatorial Race - Op-Ed Pieces by Howard Zinn (includes draft), 1990; cuid15971 (Box 25, Folder 11)
    - Silber, John: Transcript of Interview Concerning Howard Zinn (12/3/1979), cuid15972 (Box 25, Folder 12)
    - Silber, John: Writings (includes letter from Silber with Zinn annotations), 1974-1983, undated; cuid15973 (Box 25, Folder 13)
    - South Africa, Anti-Apartheid Materials, 1985-1987, undated; cuid15974 (Box 25, Folder 14)
    - Strike! Poster, 1970; cuid15975; Currently unavailable - awaiting preservation treatment (Flat-file-folder 7)
    - Strikes: 1979, 1978-1979; cuid15976 (Box 25, Folder 15)
    - Strikes: 1979 (I), cuid15977 (Box 25, Folder 16)
    - Strikes: 1979 (II), cuid15978 (Box 25, Folder 17)
    - Strikes: 1979 (III), cuid15979 (Box 25, Folder 18)
    - Strikes: 1979 (IV), cuid15980 (Box 25, Folder 19)
    - Strikes: 1979, 1979, undated; cuid15981 (Box 25, Folder 20)
    - Strikes: 1979 - Legal, 1979-1980; cuid15982 (Box 25, Folder 21)
    - Strikes: Negatives, undated; cuid15983 (Box 25, Folder 22)
    - Student Demonstration against General Electric Recruiters and Aftermath (11/25/1969), 1969-1970; cuid15984 (Box 25, Folder 23)
    - Student, Faculty Code Issues, 1970-1986; cuid15985 (Box 25, Folder 24)
    - Student Health Center (includes National Labor Relations Board Discrimination Case), 1975-1978, undated; cuid15986 (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - Student Paper: "John Silber and the BU Crisis: The Faculty Strike of 1979" by Claudia Krakowski, cuid15987 (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - Student Strike, 1970; cuid15988 (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - Teach-In February 14, 1979, cuid15989 (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - Tenure Discrimination: Brown, Julia Prewitt, 1987, 1990; cuid15990 (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - Tenure Discrimination: Brown, Julia Prewitt v. Trustees of Boston University - Transcript (Day 1), 1987; cuid15991 (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - Tenure Discrimination: Brown, Julia Prewitt v. Trustees of Boston University - Transcript (Day 2), 1987; cuid15992 (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - Tenure Discrimination: Brown, Julia Prewitt v. Trustees of Boston University - Transcript (Day 3), 1987; cuid15993 (Box 26, Folder 8)
    - Tenure Discrimination: Brown, Julia Prewitt v. Trustees of Boston University - Transcript (Day 4), 1987; cuid15994 (Box 26, Folder 9)
    - Tenure Discrimination: Brown, Julia Prewitt v. Trustees of Boston University - Transcript (Day 5), 1987; cuid15995 (Box 26, Folder 10)
    - Tenure Discrimination: Brown, Julia Prewitt v. Trustees of Boston University - Transcript (Day 6), 1987; cuid15996 (Box 26, Folder 11)
    - Tenure Discrimination: Brown, Julia Prewitt v. Trustees of Boston University - Transcript (Day 7), 1987; cuid15997 (Box 26, Folder 12)
    - Tenure Discrimination: Brown, Julia Prewitt v. Trustees of Boston University - Transcript (Day 8), 1987; cuid15998 (Box 26, Folder 13)
    - Tenure Discrimination: Brown, Julia Prewitt v. Trustees of Boston University - Transcript (Day 9), 1987; cuid15999 (Box 26, Folder 14)
    - Tenure Discrimination: Brown, Julia Prewitt v. Trustees of Boston University - Transcript (Day 10), 1987; cuid16000 (Box 26, Folder 15)
    - Tenure Discrimination: Brown, Julia Prewitt v. Trustees of Boston University - Transcript (Day 11), 1987; cuid16001 (Box 26, Folder 16)
    - Tenure Discrimination: Brown, Julia Prewitt v. Trustees of Boston University - Transcript (Day 12), 1987; cuid16002 (Box 26, Folder 17)
    - Tenure Discrimination: Brown, Julia Prewitt v. Trustees of Boston University - Transcript (Day 13 - Closing Arguments and Charge), 1987; cuid16003 (Box 26, Folder 18)
    - Tenure Discrimination: Brown, Julia Prewitt v. Trustees of Boston University - Zinn Notes, 1987; cuid16004 (Box 26, Folder 19)
    - Trustees (I), 1974-1982; cuid16005 (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - Trustees (II), 1974-1982; cuid16006 (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - Trustees, 1976-1980, 1990, undated; cuid16007 (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - Tuition Increases, 1978-1991, undated; cuid16008 (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - Vendors on Campus, 1976, 1979; cuid16009 (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - Women's Issues, 1970-1980; cuid16010 (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - Zinn Application for Metcalf Award, 1988; cuid16011 (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - Zinn Correspondence with Herman Frederick Eilts (various topics), 1983-1986; cuid16012 (Box 27, Folder 8)
    - Zinn Pay Docking Grievance, 1979-1980; cuid16013 (Box 27, Folder 9)
    - Zinn Salary, Merit Grievances, 1974-1978; cuid16014 (Box 27, Folder 10)
    - Zinn Salary, Merit Grievances, 1979; cuid16015 (Box 27, Folder 11)
    - Zinn Salary, Merit Grievances (I), 1980; cuid16016 (Box 27, Folder 12)
    - Zinn Salary, Merit Grievances (II), 1980; cuid16017 (Box 27, Folder 13)
    - Zinn Salary, Merit Grievances, 1981; cuid16018 (Box 27, Folder 14)
    - Zinn Salary, Merit Grievances, 1982-1983; cuid16019 (Box 27, Folder 15)
    - Zinn Salary, Merit Grievances, 1984-1985; cuid16020 (Box 27, Folder 16)
    - Zinn Salary, Merit Grievances, 1987; cuid16021 (Box 27, Folder 17)
    - Zinn Salary, Merit Grievances: Summaries and Emily Dalgarno (AAUP) Package, 1979-1981; cuid16022 (Box 27, Folder 18)
    - Zinn Salary, Merit Grievances: Supporting Material, 1962-1981, undated; cuid16023 (Box 27, Folder 19)
    - Zinn Salary, Merit Grievances: Supporting Material - Evaluations, 1969-1981; cuid16024 (Box 27, Folder 20)
    - Zinn Salary, Merit Grievances: Supporting Material - Evaluations, 1979-1983; cuid16025 (Box 27, Folder 21)
    - Zinn Sit-In Participation, December 8, 1969, 1970; cuid16026 (Box 27, Folder 22)
- Series VI: Race and Civil Rights, 1932-2008